Guide to the Fales Manuscript Collection circa 1700-2000 MSS.001
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Letter sized boxes
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial [various by Browne, Hablot K.], undated (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial [various by Phiz], undated (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial [Works], undated (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial [Barnaby Rudge, miscellaneous], undated (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial [Barnaby Rudge, Yeager, engraver], undated (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, The Chimes, undated (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, A Christmas Carol, undated (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, David Copperfield, by W. H. C. Groome, undated (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, Dombey, undated (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, Barnaby Rudge, undated (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, David Copperfield [Dutch], undated (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, Great Expectations [by J. Clayton Clark], undated (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, Great Expectations [pencil drawings], undated (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, Is She His Wife? [Frontispiece by F. W. Pailthorpe] [December 18, 1861] (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, Master Humphrey's Clock, undated (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, Nicholas Nickleby, undated (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, Oliver [Cruickshank drawings (great nephew, not the)], undated (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, Pickwick Plates, undated (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, Pickwick cheap edition, undated (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, Pickwick [Darley & Furniss], undated (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, Pickwick [by A. B. Frost], undated (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, Pickwick [by Gibson], undated (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, various plates, undated (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, Pickwick, Mulready & Miscellaneous Theatrical Productions [see also legal folders], undated (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, Pickwick. Leipzig edition [43 re-engravings for 1842 Weber edition], undated (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, Village Coquettes, undated (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, Various works 2, undated (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Dickensiana, clippings, undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): clippings, undated (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): clippings, undated (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): clippings, undated (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Dickensiana, clippings, undated (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Dickensiana, clippings & death notice, undated (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): photocopy, undated (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): theatre programs, undated (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, The Strange Gentleman, undated (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, "12 Extra Illustrations to The Pickwick Papers" [by Charles E. Block, 1921] (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Photograph of Nellie Bowman as Oliver Twist, undated (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pickwick Celebrites, hand colored lithograph, undated (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Dickins, Fr., undated (Box 46, Folder 1a)
  - Dickinson, Anna E. (Anna Elizabeth) (1842-1932), undated (Box 46, Folder 1b)
  - Dilke, Charles Wentworth (1789-1864), undated (Box 46, Folder 1c)
  - Disney, John (1779-1857), undated (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Disraeli, Benjamin, undated (Box 46, Folder 2a)
  - Disraeli, Isaac, undated (Box 46, Folder 2b)
  - Dix, Morgan (1827-1908), undated (Box 46, Folder 3a)
  - Dixon, Arthur A., 1892-1893 (Box 46, Folder 3b)
  - Dixon, J. H., undated (Box 46, Folder 3c)
  - Dixon, Thomas (1864-1946), undated (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Dixon, William Hepworth (1821-1879), undated (Box 46, Folder 3e)
  - Dobson, Austin (1840-1921), undated (Box 46, Folder 4a)
  - Dobson, Rosemary, undated (Box 46, Folder 4b)
  - Doctorow, Edgar L., undated (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Dodd, William, undated (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Dodge, Mary Abigail (1833-1896) (Gail Hamilton, pseud.), undated (Box 46, Folder 7a)
  - Dodge, Mary Mapes (1831-1905), undated (Box 46, Folder 7b)
  - Dodgson, Charles Lutwidge (1832-1898) (Lewis Carroll, pseud.), 1870s-1880s; undated (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Dodgson, Charles Lutwidge (1832-1898) (Lewis Carroll, pseud.): [1889-1893, to Meehan (bookseller)] (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Dodgson, Charles Lutwidge (1832-1898) (Lewis Carroll, pseud.), 1890s (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Dodgson, Charles Lutwidge (1832-1898) (Lewis Carroll, pseud.): [1893-1897, to Stevens, Enid] (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Dodgson, Charles Lutwidge (1832-1898) (Lewis Carroll, pseud.): MS. Poems ["The 8 Henrys"; "B.N.C."], undated (Box 46, Folder 12a)
  - Dodgson, Charles Lutwidge (1832-1898) (Lewis Carroll, pseud.): MS. "Dates of Treaties", undated (Box 46, Folder 12b)
  - Dodgson, Charles Lutwidge (1832-1898) (Lewis Carroll, pseud.): Carrolliana, undated (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Dodgson, Charles Lutwidge (1832-1898) (Lewis Carroll, pseud.): Memorabilia [Alice photograph; doily], undated (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Dole, Nathan Haskell, undated (Box 46.5, Folder 1a)
  - Donne, William Bodham (1807-1882), undated (Box 46.5, Folder 1b)
  - Donnelly, Ignatius (1831-1901), undated (Box 46.5, Folder 1c)
  - Dorman, Rushton, undated (Box 46.5, Folder 1)
  - Dorn, Edward: Correspondence [1964-1966, to John Wieners] (Box 46.5, Folder 2)
  - Dorr, Julia C. R. (1825-1913), undated (Box 46.5, Folder 3a)
  - Dorr, Rheta Louise (Childe), undated (Box 46.5, Folder 3b)
  - Dorsett, A., undated (Box 46.5, Folder 3c)
  - Dos Passos, John (1896- ), undated (Box 46.5, Folder 4a)
  - Dos Passos, John: A.M.s.: Red, White and Blue Thanksgiving, undated (Box 46.5, Folder 4b)
  - Dos Passos, John: A.M.s.: In Memoriam, undated (Box 46.5, Folder 4c)
  - Doubleday, Abner (1819-1893), undated (Box 46.5, Folder 5a)
  - Doubleday, William Elliot (1865-?), undated (Box 46.5, Folder 5b)
  - Douglas, Alfred (Lord) (1870-1945) [Letter to Wilde], undated (Box 46.5, Folder 6)
  - Douglas, Alfred (Lord) (1870-1945), 1917-1934 (Box 46.5, Folder 6a)
  - Douglas, Alfred (Lord) (1870-1945), 1929-1940 (Box 46.5, Folder 6b)
  - Douglas, Alfred (Lord) (1870-1945) [Transcriptions and Biographical Info], Undated (Box 46.5, Folder 6c)
  - Douglas, Lloyd Cassel (1877-1951), undated (Box 46.5, Folder 7a)
  - Douglas, Norman (1868-1952), undated (Box 46.5, Folder 7b)
  - Douglas, Norman (1868-1952): [printed material], undated (Box 46.5, Folder 8)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Andre´, Michael (Editor, Unmuzzled Ox), 1973 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Armstrong, Mike, 1966-1968 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Basak, Subimal, 1967-1975 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Beneviste, Asa and Vaughan, Paul, 1969-1973 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Berge´, Carol, 1963-1965 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Bloyek, Doug, 1966-1970 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Blomerus, Marie, 1967-1974 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Bly, Robert, 1963-1964 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Bogan, Louise, 1960-1962 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Bullock, Chris, (Editor, Bent), 1964-1966 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Choudhuri, Pradip, 1968-1975 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Cunliffe, Dave and Tina [see also Oversize], 1965-1970 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: De Loach, Allen, 1966-1973 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Dash, Tony [see also Oversize], 1968-1969 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: De Wet, Andre [South Africa], 1970-1973 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Ehrenberg, Felipe [see also Oversize], undated (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Evans, Paul, 1965-1971 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Finlay, Ian Hamilton [1964] and Fowler, Gene [1969-1970] [see also Oversize], 1964; 1969-1970 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Furnival, John, 1964-1973 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Georgakas, Dan [see also Oversize], 1967-1973 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Ginsberg, Allen [see also Oversize], 1964?-1973 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Green, Paul and Gross, Ronald, 1967-1969 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Grinberg, Miguel and Gwerda, Urban [see also Oversize], undated (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Hall, Barry; Hand, Alex [see also Oversize]; Hitchcock, George, undated (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Hollo, Anselm [see also Oversize]; Horowitz, Mike; Houe´dard, Dom Sylvester [see also Oversize], undated (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Jones, LeRoi and Kingdon, Melanie, undated (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Koch, Kenneth and Kryss, T. L., undated (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Legman, Gershon and Levertov, Denise, undated (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Levine, Stephen, (Editor, Unity Press), 1968-1974 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Levy, D. A. [see also Oversize]; Lowell, Jim [see also Oversize]; Lowenfells, Walter, undated (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Loynes, Ken (Editor, Hapt) [see also Oversize], undated (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: McCarthy, Cavan (Editor, Tlaloc), undated (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: McClure, Michael; McCord, Howard; MacDonogh, Steve; Manganotti, Donatella, undated (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Mann, Peter [see also Legal Size], undated (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Matthews, Paul (Editor, 11th Finger), undated (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Menarini, Gianni, undated (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Middleton, Fred, undated (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Morgan, Pete, undated (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Mottram, Eric [see also Legal Size], undated (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Nuttall, Jeff [see also Legal Size], undated (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Patten, Brian; Prigent, Michael, undated (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Raworth, Tom, 1963-1969 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Rothenberg, Jerome, 1963-1969 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Sanders, Ed; Saxon, Dan [see also Oversize]; Sewell, Brocard, undated (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Sigmund, R. J. [see also Levy, D. A. and Oversize], undated (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Sinclair, Iain [see also Oversize]; Sohn, Hans; Sottsass, Fernanda, undated (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Telling, Derek, (Editor, Imprint), undated (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Wagner, D.R. [see also Oversize], undated (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Wilder, Thornton, undated (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Weissner, Carl (Editor, Klact), undated (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Whalen, Philip and Williams, Jonathan, undated (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Dowden, George: MS. Flight from America, undated (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Dowden, George: MS. Poems, undated (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Downes, George, undated (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Doyle, Arthur Conan, Sir (1859-1930), undated (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Doyle, Francis Hastings Charles, Sir (1810-1888), undated (Box 50, Folder 3a)
  - Doyle, Richard (1824-1883), undated (Box 50, Folder 3b)
  - Doyle, Thomas (1793-1879), undated (Box 50, Folder 3c)
  - Draper, Amy, undated (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Dreiser, Theodore (1871-1945), 1907-1925 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Dreiser, Theodore (1871-1945): [see also Oversize], 1926-1945 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Drinkwater, John (1882-1937), undated (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Drinkwater, John (1882-1937): MS. X=O: a Night in the Trojan War, undated (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Drury, Allen: A God Against the Gods (a novel), undated (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Drummond, William Henry (1854-1907), undated (Box 52, Folder 1a)
  - Drury, Allen Stuart, undated (Box 52, Folder 1b)
  - Dudley, Ambrose, undated (Box 52, Folder 1c)
  - Dumas, Alexandre (1802-1870): [see also Flat], undated (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - DuMaurier, Daphne, undated (Box 52, Folder 3a)
  - DuMaurier, George (1834-1896), undated (Box 52, Folder 3b)
  - Dunbar, Paul, undated (Box 52, Folder 4a)
  - Duncan, Robert: MS. Towards an Open Universe, undated (Box 52, Folder 4b)
  - Duncan, Todd, undated (Box 52, Folder 4c)
  - Dunne, Finley Peter, undated (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Dunsany, Beatrice (Villiers), undated (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Dunsany, Edward John Moreton Drax Plunkett, Baron (1878-1957), 1905-1930 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Dunsany, Edward John Moreton Drax Plunkett, Baron (1878-1957), 1931-1952; undated (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Dunsany, Edward John Moreton Drax Plunkett, Baron (1878-1957): to Tarshish, Manuel B., 1946-1948 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Dunsany, Edward John Moreton Drax Plunkett, Baron (1878-1957): to Tarshish, Manuel B., 1949-1952 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Dunsany, Edward John Moreton Drax Plunkett, Baron (1878-1957): to Tarshish, Manuel B. [envelopes 1946-1952] (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Dunsany, Edward John Moreton Drax Plunkett, Baron (1878-1957): Tarshish, Miscellaneous clippings and photographs, undated (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Dunsany, Edward John Moreton Drax Plunkett, Baron (1878-1957): 6 Letters to Lord Dunsany, from Sime, Sidney H. [Elkin Matthews], 3 Checks - Elkin Matthews, undated (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Dunsany, Edward John Moreton Drax Plunkett, Baron (1878-1957): miscellaneous MSS., undated (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Durrell, Lawrence (1912- ), undated (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Dusoir, Ilse: The History of the Seven Arts (NYU Masters Thesis, Sept. 1940), undated (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Dwight, Harrison Griswold (1875- ), undated (Box 52, Folder 16a)
  - Dyce, Alexander (1798-1869), undated (Box 52, Folder 16b)
  - Eadie, Dennis, undated (Box 53, Folder 1a)
  - Eagle, Paul: MS. "You"; "Lucky Room", undated (Box 53, Folder 1b)
  - Earle, Alice (Morse), undated (Box 53, Folder 1c)
  - East Lake, Charles Locke, Sir (1793-1865), undated (Box 53, Folder 2a)
  - East Lake, Elizabeth (Rigby), Lady (1809-1893), undated (Box 53, Folder 2b)
  - Eastman, Max, undated (Box 53, Folder 3a)
  - Eberhardt, Richard: MS. "Love Pieces", undated (Box 53, Folder 3b)
  - Ebers, John (1785?-1830?), undated (Box 53, Folder 3c)
  - Eckerley, Eva, undated (Box 53, Folder 4a)
  - Eddis, Edin Upton (1812-1901), undated (Box 53, Folder 4b)
  - Edel, Leon, undated (Box 53, Folder 4c)
  - Eden, Emily (1797-1869), undated (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Edersheim, Sophia (Hancock), undated (Box 53, Folder 4e)
  - Edgeworth, Maria (1767-1849): [see also Map Case], 1803-1830 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Edgeworth, Maria (1767-1849), 1831-1848 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Edgeworth, Maria (1767-1849), undated (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Edison, Thomas Alva [from his secretary], undated (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Edwards, Amelia (Ann Blandford) (1831-1892), undated (Box 53, Folder 9a)
  - Edwards, George Wharton, undated (Box 53, Folder 9b)
  - Egan, Maurice Francis (1852-1924), undated (Box 53, Folder 9c)
  - Egan, Maurice Francis (1852-1924): MS. An Old-Fashioned View of the Art of Fiction, undated (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Egg, Augustus, undated (Box 53, Folder 9e)
  - Eggleston, Edward (1837-1902), undated (Box 53, Folder 10a)
  - Eggleston, George Cary (1839-1911), undated (Box 53, Folder 10b)
  - Eigner, Larry [to Tom Clark and Andrew Crozier, 1966 (includes MSS.)] (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Eigner, Larry [to Weil, James, 1970-1973] (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Eigner, Larry: MS. Anything on its Side, undated (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Eigner, Larry: MS. Shape Shadow Elements, undated (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Eldridge, Paul, undated (Box 53, Folder 15a)
  - Eliot, Charles William (1834-1926), undated (Box 53, Folder 15b)
  - Eliot, George [Mary Ann Cross, ne´e Evans] (1819-1880), 1848-1880; undated (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Eliot, Thomas Stearns (1888- ), 1931-1959 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Eliot, Thomas Stearns: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Ellesmere, Francis Egerton, 1st Earl of (1800-1857), undated (Box 53, Folder 19a)
  - Ellis, Florence T., undated (Box 53, Folder 19b)
  - Ellis, Havelock (1859-1939), 1914-1930; undated (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Ellis, Havelock: MS. Concerning Jude the Obscure [see also Galleys], undated (Box 53, Folder 21a)
  - Ellis, Havelock: MS. The Making of Rousseau, undated (Box 53, Folder 21b)
  - Ellis, Sir Henry (1777-1869), undated (Box 54, Folder 1a)
  - Ellis, Sarah, undated (Box 54, Folder 1b)
  - Elmendorf, John Jay (1827-1896), undated (Box 54, Folder 1c)
  - Ely, Alwyn, undated (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Ellison, James Whitfield, undated (Box 54, Folder 1e)
  - Embury, Lucy [Hubbell], undated (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Emerson, Ralph Waldo, undated (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Emery, George, undated (Box 54, Folder 4a)
  - Emmet, Robert, undated (Box 54, Folder 4b)
  - Empson, William (1791-1852), undated (Box 54, Folder 4c)
  - Empson, William (1906- ), undated (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Erman, A., undated (Box 54, Folder 5a)
  - Erskine, John (1879-1951), undated (Box 54, Folder 5b)
  - Ervine, St. John Greer (1883- ), undated (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Etty, William [painter] (1787-1849), undated (Box 54, Folder 7a)
  - Eustis, George Tickner, undated (Box 54, Folder 7b)
  - Evans, Evan (1731-1789), undated (Box 54, Folder 7c)
  - Evans, Caradoc, undated (Box 54, Folder 8a)
  - Evans, Paul: 4 A.L.s.; MS. Listen, It's Blue, undated (Box 54, Folder 8b)
  - Evarts, Hal George (1887- ), undated (Box 54, Folder 9a)
  - Evelyn, George, undated (Box 54, Folder 9b)
  - Everett, Edward (1794-1865), undated (Box 54, Folder 9c)
  - Ewart, Wilfred, undated (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Faber, Leslie, undated (Box 54, Folder 11a)
  - Faithful, Emily, undated (Box 54, Folder 11b)
  - Faraday, Michael (1791-1867), undated (Box 54, Folder 12a)
  - Fargus, Frederick John (1847-1885), undated (Box 54, Folder 12b)
  - Farjeon, Benjamin L. (1838-1903), undated (Box 54, Folder 12c)
  - Farjeon, Eleanor (1881- ), undated (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Farnol, Jeffery (1878-1952): Correspondence, Photographs, undated (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Farnol, Jeffery (1878-1952): MSS. Broad Highway, Vol. 2, Chapters 19-26, undated (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Farnol, Jeffery (1878-1952): MS. Feet of Clay, undated (Box 54, Folder 15a)
  - Farnol, Jeffery (1878-1952): MS. The Philosopher in the Garden, undated (Box 54, Folder 15b)
  - Farnol, Jeffery (1878-1952): MS. With the Supers in Shenandoah, undated (Box 54, Folder 15c)
  - Farnol, Jeffery (1878-1952): MS. The Interlopers, undated (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Farnol, Jeffery (1878-1952): MS. The Spotted Snake, undated (Box 54, Folder 15e)
  - Farnol, Jeffery (1878-1952): miscellaneous fragments, undated (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Farnol, Jeffery (1878-1952): 4 unidentified MSS., undated (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Farrar, Frederic William (1831-1903), undated (Box 54.5, Folder 1)
  - Farrell, James Thomas (1904- ), undated (Box 54.5, Folder 2)
  - Fast, Howard, undated (Box 54.5, Folder 3)
  - Faulkner, William (1897-1962), undated (Box 54.5, Folder 4)
  - Fawcett, Edgar (1847-1909), undated (Box 54.5, Folder 5a)
  - Fawcett, Millicent Garrett, Dame (1847-1929), 1900 (Box 54.5, Folder 5b)
  - Fay, Theodore Sedgwick (1807-1898), undated (Box 54.5, Folder 6)
  - Fearing, Kenneth, undated (Box 54.5, Folder 7a)
  - Featherstonhaugh, George William (1780-1866), undated (Box 54.5, Folder 7b)
  - Fechter, Charles Albert (1824-1879), undated (Box 54.5, Folder 8)
  - Felton, Cornelius Conway (1807-1862), undated (Box 54.5, Folder 9a)
  - Fenn, George Manville (1831-1909), undated (Box 54.5, Folder 9b)
  - Ferber, Edna, undated (Box 54.5, Folder 10)
  - Ferber, Edna: MS. No Foolin'; 5 T.L.s.; 2 T.L.s. to Ferber; [see also Galleys], undated (Box 54.5, Folder 11)
  - Ferber, Edna: MS. Long Distance, undated (Box 54.5, Folder 12)
  - Ferber, Edna: MS. No Room at the Inn, undated (Box 54.5, Folder 13)
  - Ferber, Edna: MS. Hey! Taxi!, undated (Box 54.5, Folder 14)
  - Ferlinghetti, Lawrence, undated (Box 54.5, Folder 15a)
  - Fernandes, Angelo, undated (Box 54.5, Folder 15b)
  - Ferrier, Susan Edmond Stone (1782-1854), undated (Box 54.5, Folder 15c)
  - Fessenden, Samuel (1784-1869), undated (Box 54.5, Folder 16a)
  - Few, William (1748-1828), undated (Box 54.5, Folder 16b)
  - Field, Eugene: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Field, Eugene: MS. The Wanderer, undated (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Field, Eugene: MS. The Dock, undated (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Field, Kate, undated (Box 55, Folder 4a)
  - Field, R. M.: 1 Letter, undated (Box 55, Folder 4b)
  - Field, William B. Osgood: Edward Lear [pp. 1-168], undated (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Field, William B. Osgood: Edward Lear [pp. 185-340], undated (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Field, William B. Osgood, undated (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Field, William B. Osgood, undated (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Fielding, Copley, undated (Box 55.5, Folder 1a)
  - Fielding, John, Sir (d. 1780), undated (Box 55.5, Folder 1b)
  - Fielding, William J. (William John) (1886- ), 1967 (Box 55.5, Folder 1c)
  - Fields, Annie Adams (1834-1915), undated (Box 55.5, Folder 2a)
  - Fields, James T. (1817-1881), undated (Box 55.5, Folder 2b)
  - Figgis, Darrell, undated (Box 55.5, Folder 3a)
  - Finck, H. T., undated (Box 55.5, Folder 3b)
  - Finden, Edward F. (1791-1857), undated (Box 55.5, Folder 3c)
  - Finley, E. F. Scott, undated (Box 55.5, Folder 3)
  - Finley, John Huston, undated (Box 55.5, Folder 3e)
  - Firbank, Ronald (1886-1926): Correspondence to Heather Firbank (sister) [1898-1922] (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Firbank, Ronald (1886-1926): Correspondence to Heather Firbank (sister) [1923-July 1924], 1923-1924 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Firbank, Ronald (1886-1926): Correspondence to Heather Firbank (sister) [Aug.-Dec. 1924] (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Firbank, Ronald (1886-1926): Correspondence to Heather Firbank (sister) [1925-1926] (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Firbank, Ronald (1886-1926): Correspondence to Heather Firbank (sister), undated (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Firbank, Ronald (1886-1926): Correspondence [1924-1925] (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Firbank, Ronald (1886-1926): Correspondence from Brentanos, N.Y. [1924-1925] [see also Legal Size] (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Firbank, Ronald (1886-1926): Correspondence from Carew, Helen [undated] (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Firbank, Ronald (1886-1926): Correspondence from Holland, Vyvyan, 1913-1925 (Box 56, Folder 9)